/* jshint esversion: 6 */
/* jshint -W033 */

// Questions - Fearless

export const fearlessQuestions = [
    {
    "question": "You take my hand and drag me head first",
    "answers": ["Fifteen", "Breathe", "Fearless", "Love Story"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "And you're dancing 'round your room when the night ends",
    "answers": ["The Way I Loved You", "The Best Day", "Change", "Fifteen"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You'll be the prince and I'll be the princess",
    "answers": ["Love Story", "White Horse", "Breathe", "Untouchable"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I could give you 50 reasons why I should be the one you choose",
    "answers": ["Change", "Hey Stephen", "Jump Then Fall", "You're Not Sorry"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "This ain't Hollywood, this is a small town",
    "answers": ["White Horse", "The Way I Loved You", "Love Story", "Fifteen"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "And you've got a smile that can light up this whole town",
    "answers": ["Breathe", "You Belong With Me", "White Horse", "Change"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Every little bump in the road I tried to swerve",
    "answers": ["The Way I Loved You", "Hey Stephen", "Breathe", "The Best Day"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Why do you have to put down my dreams so you're the only thing on my mind?",
    "answers": ["Change", "Tell Me Why", "The Other Side of the Door", "Come in with the Rain"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "You used to shine so bright but I watched all of it fade ",
    "answers": ["You're Not Sorry", "Tell Me Why", "The Other Side of the Door", "Come in with the Rain"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You're so in love that you act insane",
    "answers": ["Fearless", "White Horse", "Change", "The Way I Loved You"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Here's to silence, that cuts me to the core",
    "answers": ["Love Story", "Breathe", "Forever & Always", "Jump then Fall"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "It's the age of princesses and pirate ships",
    "answers": ["The Best Day", "Untouchable", "Superstar", "The Other Side of the Door"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "These walls that they put up to hold us back will fall down",
    "answers": ["Jump then Fall", "Come in with the Rain", "Change", "Today was a Fairytale"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "The bottom's gonna drop out from under our feet",
    "answers": ["Today was a Fairytale", "Jump then Fall", "Superstar", "Love Story"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And now that you're close I feel like coming undone",
    "answers": ["Untouchable", "Breathe", "Fifteen", "White Horse"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I could stand up and sing you a song but I don't wanna have to go that far",
    "answers": ["The Best Day", "Come in with the Rain", "Forever & Always", "You're Not Sorry"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "So dim that spotlight, tell me things like `I can't take my eyes off of you`",
    "answers": ["Jump Then Fall", "Untouchable", "You Belong With Me", "Superstar"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "After everything and that little black dress",
    "answers": ["The Other Side of the Door", "Forever & Always", "Fifteen", "Hey Stephen"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You'll be the prince and I'll be the princess",
    "answers": ["Love Story", "The Way I Loved You", "Breathe", "Fearless"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "But I miss screaming and fighting and kissing in the rain",
    "answers": ["Forever & Always", "The Way I Loved You", "The Best Day", "Tell Me Why"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "It rains when you're here and it rains when you're gone",
    "answers": ["Hey Stephen", "Fifteen", "Forever & Always", "Change"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "You're the only thing I know like the back of my hand",
    "answers": ["Love Story", "Breathe", "White Horse", "Fearless"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And we'll sing hallelujah, we'll sing hallelujah",
    "answers": ["Change", "Fifteen", "You Belong with Me", "Love Story"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I'm not a princess, this ain't a fairy tale",
    "answers": ["Tell me Why", "Fearless", "Jump Then Fall", "White Horse"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "'Cause I'm too tired at night to call your name",
    "answers": ["Superstar", "Come in with the Rain", "The Other Side of the Door", "Change"],
    "correct": 1
    },
];